# Abdulrahman Alshafei



Undergraduate Student

Self-motivated web developer adds high level of experience over more than 2 years collaborating and working on multiple webbased projects. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reachability and security. Organized approach to meeting multiple, concurrent deadlines. Pulls from active knowledge of current technology landscape to promote best practices in web design. Applying agile and CI/CD project management methodology in the workflow.

## Work History

#### 2019-04 -Fullstack Web Developer 2019-08

Completed more than 5 projects focusing on how to make a fully functional web application covering topics including:

- SQL and Data Modeling for the Web
- API Development and Documentation
- Identity Access Management
- Server Deployment and Containerization as part of Udacity's fullstack nanodegree program.

## Education

2018-10 - Current	Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Science And Engineering	
	Faculty Of Electronic Engineering - Menoufia, Egypt	
2016-10 -	Thanaweya Amma: Mathematics	
2018-07	Al-Shahid Ahmed Salama - Menoufia, Egypt	

## **Accomplishments**

Won the Bronze Medal at ICT Competition 2018-2019 Cloud Track.

## Certifications

2019-05	Huawei Certificate (HCIA-Storage)
2019-07	Huawei Certificate (HCIA-AI)
2019-05	Huawei Certificate Cloud Track
2020-08	Udacity Fullstack Nanodegree Certificate
2019-02	Microsoft Certificate (Business skils)

#### Contact

#### Address

Menouf, Menoufia, 32951

#### Phone

01555369706

#### E-mall

ab.al.shafei@eleng.menofia.edu.eg

#### Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/abdulrah man-elshafei-4

## Skills

Python	0000
JavaScript	••••
NodeJS	••••
SQL	••••
Database Mar	
REST AP	••••
GraphQL	••••
Docker	••••
Kubernetes	••••
AWS	••••
React	••••
HTML	••••
CSS	••••
Git	••••
Github	••••
Heroku	••••
Firebase	••••

## Languages

Arabic

English

